<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Come To Toronto</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="beaches">Beaches</string>
    <string name="things">Things To Do In Toronto</string>

    <!-- Beaches strings -->
    <string name="sunny_title">SUNNYSIDE BEACH</string>
    <string name="sunny">Sunnyside Beach is the closest it’s been to the hub of activity it represented before the Gardiner cut it off from the rest of the city in 1955. Following a section of the Martin Goodman Trail, its lake air and lapping waves make it a preferred commuting route for west end cyclists, rollerbladers and joggers, Sunnyside Pavilion is a popular rendezvous for watersports like competitive rowing, stand up paddleboarding, and canoe and kayak rentals, and the sandy patches that dot the coast are alive with sunbathers, Frisbee, and beach volleyball, and while the beach isn’t always safe for swimming, there’s always the free pool.</string>
    <string name="islands_title">Toronto Islands</string>
    <string name="islands">Park consisting of four main islands and containing trails, beaches and children\'s amusement rides.</string>
    <string name="cherry_title">Cherry Beach</string>
    <string name="cherry">One of the Port Lands’s few saving graces, Cherry Beach offers the industrial neighbourhood a leafy green contrast and attractive integration with Lake Ontario. Added bonus for seaworthy beach bums: it’s conveniently situated across the channel from Ward’s Island, so save your ferry fare.</string>
    <string name="marie_title">MARIE CURTIS PARK BEACH</string>
    <string name="marie">Hinging Toronto and Mississauga at the mouth of Etobicoke Creek in Long Branch, the beach at Marie Curtis Park is a tranquil space flanked by willow trees and suburban housing. At the intersection of several communities and their shared histories, it was originally created in the late 1950s to help control flooding after Hurricane Hazel swept Lake Ontario. Today, City of Toronto parks staff are working with the Region of Peel and Credit Valley Conservation on a design for a new greenspace that will connect the park with the Inspiration Lakeview Lands.</string>
    <string name="sugar_title">SUGAR BEACH</string>
    <string name="sugar">Like the urban beach at HTO Park, Sugar Beach is another sandy bar with Muskoka chairs and big shady umbrellas that look out onto Lake Ontario, but here they’re powder pink. And no, no swimming here, either, so you won’t have to share those seats with abandoned towels.</string>

    <!-- Hotels strings -->
    <string name="grand_title">Grand Hotel</string>
    <string name="grand">This luxurious hotel features a rooftop patio with heated whirlpools overlooking the city centre of Toronto. Guests may enjoy a gourmet restaurant and free Wi-Fi. Union Station is 2 km away.</string>
    <string name="tree_title">DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Toronto Downtown</string>
    <string name="tree">Located in the city centre, DoubleTree by Hilton Toronto Downtown boasts an indoor heated pool, an on-site restaurant, and a fitness centre. Toronto Eaton Centre and St. Patrick Subway Station are within 350 m.\n</string>
    <string name="rena_title">Renaissance Toronto Downtown Hotel</string>
    <string name="rena">This 4-star hotel in Toronto is located in the Rogers Centre sports and entertainment complex. The hotel features Arriba, a Mediterranean restaurant, and an indoor pool. Pearson International Airport is 26 km away.\n</string>
    <string name="marriott_title">Toronto Marriott Downtown Eaton Centre Hotel</string>
    <string name="marriott">Located in Toronto Eaton Centre, this hotel is connected to PATH underground walkway. Trios Bistro is on site and a 32-inch flat-screen TV is featured in rooms. Dundas Subway Station is 350 m away.\n</string>
    <string name="shang_title">Shangri-La Hotel Toronto</string>
    <string name="shang">Centrally located between Toronto\'s Financial and Entertainment Districts, this luxury hotel offers an indoor pool, hot tub and on-site restaurant. An iPad is featured in all the guest rooms.\n</string>

    <!-- Places to go strings -->
    <string name="high_title">High Park</string>
    <string name="high">Popular urban oasis offers a variety of outdoor recreation including ice-skating, baseball games, nature hikes and exploring the park\'s greenhouse.\n</string>
    <string name="aqua_title">Ripley\'s Aquarium Of Canada</string>
    <string name="aqua">Explore the Waters of the World at Ripley\'s Aquarium of Canada. Located in the heart of downtown Toronto at the base of the CN Tower, the aquarium is Toronto\'s newest must-see attraction for tourists and locals of all ages.\n</string>
    <string name="cn_title">CN Tower</string>
    <string name="cn">The CN Tower is a National icon, engineering Wonder, a Toronto must-see attraction and award winning dining and entertainment destination. Rocket to the top aboard the Tower\'s glass fronted and glass floor paneled elevators which take you to the top in only 58 seconds. Take in spectacular views of up to 160km (100 miles) away from four observation areas on three levels, including the LookOut, world famous Glass Floor with outdoor SkyTerrace and the SkyPod, the highest of them all. Experience the thrill of EdgeWalk at the CN Tower, the World\'s Highest Outdoor Walk on a Building. Enjoy award-winning Canadian cuisine and breathtaking revolving views at 360 The Restaurant at the CN Tower, family friendly fare at Horizons Toronto celebrating the multicultural flavours of Toronto neighbourhoods, or grab and go fare from Le Café. Plus, visual displays, KidZone play area and 8,000 square feet of unique Canadian artisan and souvenir shopping in the Gift Shop. Don\'t miss the architectural illumination of the CN Tower each night from dusk with top of the hour light show.\n</string>
    <string name="rom_title">Royal Ontario Museum</string>
    <string name="rom">The Royal Ontario Museum (ROM) is among the world’s leading museums of natural history and world cultures. In combining a universal museum of cultures with that of natural history, the ROM offers an unusual breadth of experience to our audiences from around the world. We realize more acutely now that nature and humanity are intertwined, and the ROM offers many examples in its collections and programs of these fundamental relationships.\n</string>

    <!-- restaurants strings -->
    <string name="alo_title">ALO</string>
    <string name="alo">Origin: Latin; Alui altum; To nourish, cherish, support, sustain, maintain and keep.It is our intention to get back to the roots of hospitality. We want each and every guest to feel welcome in our home, and that home is ALO. A destination for classically prepared, meticulously thought out French food and service. This no-nonsense approach to fine dining with our combined experience working behind-the-scenes at some of the world’s best restaurants has led us to this point. We welcome you to ALO.</string>
    <string name="Scaramouche_title">Scaramouche Restaurant</string>
    <string name="scaramouche">"   Scaramouche has long been celebrated by customers and critics for its unwavering commitment to making each dining experience a memorable one. Chef/owner Keith Froggett's sophisticated cuisine is presented simply with care and attention to detail. The service underscores that philosophy: unobtrusive and respectful. The restaurant affords a stunning nighttime vista of the downtown Toronto skyline. These components and more make Scaramouche the singular destination it is. And the reason that the restaurant is consistently ranked as one of the city's best for more than three decades."</string>
    <string name="richmond_title">Richmond Station</string>
    <string name="richmond">Richmond Station is a stopping place, a bustling neighbourhood restaurant in the downtown core. We are committed to delicious food and excellent hospitality.</string>
    <string name="pai_title">Pai Northern Thai Kitchen</string>
    <string name="pai">" AND WE ARE PROUD TO BOAST THAT WE DO THINGS THE WAY THEY ARE MEANT TO BE, WITH NO QUALITY CUTTING SHORT CUTS.\nWE SERVE DISHES THAT ARE INSPIRED BY CHEF NUIT'S LIFE IN NORTHERN THAILAND AND ALSO CURRENT NORTHERN THAI TRENDS"</string>
    <string name="jacob_title"><![CDATA[Jacobs & Co. Steakhouse]]></string>
    <string name="jacob"><![CDATA[In the heart of King West village, Jacobs & Co. is the mature steakhouse of the next generation.\n]]></string>
</resources>
